<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>rchute.com</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://www.rchute.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://www.rchute.com/"/>
  <updated>2020-10-28T03:34:22.623Z</updated>
  <id>http://www.rchute.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Ryan Chute</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>hello-world</title>
    <link href="http://www.rchute.com/2020/10/25/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://www.rchute.com/2020/10/25/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2020-10-25T21:38:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2020-10-28T03:34:22.623Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<html><head></head><body><p>Interesting to think we&#x2019;ve been iterating through this new world order since late March 2020.  It&#x2019;s now late October 2020 and it feels far longer than the 7 or so calendar months.  We&#x2019;ve gone through toilet paper shortages and home confinement, and now experience life in very different ways.  We are blessed with 5 active children who minimize the isolation of this time, and maximize the need to still experience life; we&#x2019;ve refined our skills at skateboarding, surfing, biking, bodyboarding, etc and rank Summer 2020 pretty high.  </p><p>We are less than a week away from the next election and one can only hope our nation has enough sense to see though the lies and misdirection to elect a transitional figure, who will help the nation address this pandemic and begin to heal.  </p><p>Beyond politics, we need a more communal approach to life.  We&#x2019;re working on being creative about how we can help others during these interesting times.  One area I&#x2019;m familar with is online marketing for small/medium online retailers.  This is where I&#x2019;d like to focus some of my extra energy and skills.  Over the last decade I&#x2019;ve built software to market retail products through the top marketing channels.  This is my kickoff to expand a side project, roicontrast.com, which will provide tools for merchants looking to expand their marketing reach.</p></body></html>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting to think we&amp;#x2019;ve been iterating through this new world order since late March 2020.  It&amp;#x2019;</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="technology" scheme="http://www.rchute.com/categories/technology/"/>
    
    <category term="life" scheme="http://www.rchute.com/categories/life/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
